Kalyn Williams

* kalynsimonewilliams@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Efficient recent college graduate with a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Digital Media Minor in Computer Science, with 3+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage academic experience and proven knowledge of desktop technology, operating system, and diagnostic testing to successfully fill the technology role at your company.

EXPERIENCE

BESTBUY, Vacaville, CA

Geek Squad Agent, Apr 2021 - Present

- Answer user inquiries regarding computer software or hardware operation to resolve problems. Worked with customers one on one to diagnose and repair computer equipment. Install and perform minor repairs to hardware, software, or peripheral equipment, following design or installation specifications. Follow up with customers to ensure their technical issues are resolved.
- Read technical manuals, confer with users, or conduct computer diagnostics to investigate and resolve problems or to provide technical assistance and support.
- Refer major hardware or software problems or defective products to vendors or technicians for service. Dealt with manufacturer warranty issues and repairs.
- Maintain records of daily data communication transactions, problems and remedial actions taken, or installation activities while accurately troubleshooting and notating various issues within a ticketing system(NOVA).
- Prepared evaluations of software or hardware, and recommend improvements or upgrades.
- Prepared returned units for reselling by cleaning resetting and running diagnostics on units.

Computer Consultant, Apr 2019 - Jan 2021

- Emphasize product features based on analyses of customers' needs and on technical knowledge of product capabilities and limitations.
- Provide customers with ongoing technical support.

INTUVO, Soquel, CA

Customer Care, Nov 2019 - Jul 2020

- Perform data administration, data integrity, and data cleansing for import of data for thousands of postcard and emails a week.
- Promptly answered 10+ questions a day using a ticketing system called Jira to guarantee all troubleshooting questions are being answered and understood in non-technical terms.
- Utilized SQL reporting for use of the CRM email system errors.
- Writing detailed notes about bugs in software to tier 2 and tier 3 support.
- Creates test data to prove all test cases. Executes and documents results of test plans to ensure modules will operate properly in the production environment.
- Work with the Product team to organize market kickoffs to educate markets on new functionality.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA-SANTA CRUZ Santa Cruz, CA

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) Digital Media Minor in Computer Science (Dec 2021)

• Relevant Coursework: Database Systems, Web Applications, Mobile Applications, Introduction to Software Engineering, Fundamentals of Digital Media Production, Digital Media Workshop: Computer as Medium, Advanced Topics in Digital and Electronic Media Studies

• Extracurricular Activities: National Society of Black Engineers and Scientist

CONTRA COSTA COLLEGE San Pablo, CA

Associate in Arts (A.A.) Math and Science (May 2016)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- SQL
- JAVA
- HTML
- CSS
- · Agile methodologies and project management

CERTIFICATIONS

- Apple GSX iPhone Repair and Troubleshooting
- Apple GSX Mac Repair and Troubleshooting
- Google IT
- Sumo Logic Fundamentals

REFERENCES

References available upon request